Trust, but Verify
Reagan is a history, drama film directed by Sean McNamara.
Told through the voice of former KGB agent Viktor Petrovich, whose life becomes inextricably linked with Ronald Reagan's when Reagan first
caught the Soviets’ attention as an actor in Hollywood, Reagan overcomes the odds to become the 40th president of the United States.
Ronald Reagan, played by Dennis Quaid.
Nancy Reagan, played by Penelope Ann Miller.
Viktor Petrovich, played by Jon Voight.
Jack Warner, played by Kevin Dillon.
Mikhail Gorbachev, played by Olek Krupa.
Young Reagan, played by David Henrie.
Reagan is a 2024 American biographical drama film directed by Sean McNamara and written by Howard
Klausner, based on Paul Kengor's 2006 book The Crusader: Ronald Reagan and the Fall of Communism.
The film stars Dennis Quaid as President Ronald Reagan, alongside Penelope Ann
Miller, Jon Voight, Kevin Dillon, David Henrie, and Mena Suvari.
Filming began on September 9, 2020, and included
locations such as Guthrie, Oklahoma.
Reagan was theatrically released in the United States on August 30, 2024.
It received negative reviews from critics and at the 45th Golden Raspberry Awards was nominated for 6 Razzie Awards including
Worst Actor for Dennis Quaid and earning Jon Voight the Worst Supporting Actor award and grossed $30.1 million.
The film explores themes of usa president, politics,
affectation, biography, based on true story.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.